Just by closing my eyes, I can visualize that scene.
Wait, Yuu-chan!
Really, should you be leaving your family behind like this?
Idiot. I don't have a family.
Yeah, yeah. You keep saying that.
But the whole Hyakuya Orphanage is already your family!
Hey!
We're not your family?
C'mon, don't say that Yuu-nii!
No, we definitely are.
Isn't that right, Yuu-chan?
Sheesh, there's just no arguing with you guys.
A scene of my precious family, friends and their smiles...
Followed by their murder at the hands of a vampire.
R-Run, Yuu-chan!
Go...
Hurry!
Yuu-chan...
Mika!
Even after four years,
I only need to close my eyes for that scene to play out vividly in my mind.
Damn, a Horseman of John!
Private Hyakuya! What are you doing here?
Retreat at once!
Huh? Retreat? Who do you think you're talking to?
I live only to take revenge on the vampires.
I'll be damned if I can't even kill something like this!
That guy... every time!
I don't want nobody to get killed
I'll come and get you, I'm armed, always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame, we're wrong as well
ah wait, don't take all of the weight, you always do
There will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome, your salvation has begun
No sounds, no lights, such a mess all over
Don't kill your hopes
You make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold down the changes somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you by dawn in the shadows of the earth,
and you shall survive
Look forward and then just run,
let them know it is a pain that makes us all human after all
It's not too late to save you, of that I am sure
You found your precious world, but discard it, respond to the call
Mankind in the Aftermath
Seriously...
Why am I suspended for disobeying orders when I defeated the monster?
And why do I have to attend a civilian school anyway?
Hey, Hyakuya Yuuichirou!
What are you grumbling about?
We're in the middle of class.
What's with that attitude?
I'll expel you if you don't start taking me seriously!
Eh? You'd expel me? Seriously!?
Well then, please do!
Stop joking around!
You're just making fun of me, aren't you?
Whatever, just sit down.
Hmm?
What?
Who are you?
Huh?
I am Hiiragi Shinoa.
I'm an observation officer from the army.
If I get the impression that you aren't
cooperating, I'll report to the army and
have your suspension prolonged.
I am Hiiragi Shinoa.
I'm an observation officer from the army.
If I get the impression that you aren't
cooperating, I'll report to the army and
have your suspension prolonged.
I am Hiiragi Shinoa.
I'm an observation officer from the army.
If I get the impression that you aren't
cooperating, I'll report to the army and
have your suspension prolonged.
I am Hiiragi Shinoa.
I'm an observation officer from the army.
If I get the impression that you aren't
cooperating, I'll report to the army and
have your suspension prolonged.
I am Hiiragi Shinoa.
I'm an observation officer from the army.
If I get the impression that you aren't
cooperating, I'll report to the army and
have your suspension prolonged.
I am Hiiragi Shinoa.
I'm an observation officer from the army.
If I get the impression that you aren't
cooperating, I'll report to the army and
have your suspension prolonged.
I am Hiiragi Shinoa.
I'm an observation officer from the army.
If I get the impression that you aren't
cooperating, I'll report to the army and
have your suspension prolonged.
I am Hiiragi Shinoa.
I'm an observation officer from the army.
If I get the impression that you aren't
cooperating, I'll report to the army and
have your suspension prolonged.
I am Hiiragi Shinoa.
I'm an observation officer from the army.
If I get the impression that you aren't
cooperating, I'll report to the army and
have your suspension prolonged.
I am Hiiragi Shinoa.
I'm an observation officer from the army.
If I get the impression that you aren't
cooperating, I'll report to the army and
have your suspension prolonged.
I am Hiiragi Shinoa.
I'm an observation officer from the army.
If I get the impression that you aren't
cooperating, I'll report to the army and
have your suspension prolonged.
I am Hiiragi Shinoa.
I'm an observation officer from the army.
If I get the impression that you aren't
cooperating, I'll report to the army and
have your suspension prolonged.
I'm an observation officer from the army.
If I get the impression that you aren't
cooperating, I'll report to the army and
have your suspension prolonged.
I am Hiiragi Shinoa.
"If I get the impression that you aren't cooperating,
I'll report to the army and have your suspension prolonged."
Huh!?
What the hell are you talking about!?
Hyakuya! If you keep interrupting my class—
This is bullshit!
"Bullshit"!?
"Cooperate."
Let's continue the lesson.
By the way, this suspension will last forever if you don't make friends.
So, try to make some.
What in the world is going on?
Wasn't humanity wiped out?
Wiped out?
Is that what the vampires told you?
It's true that, thanks to that virus,
mankind was reduced to a tenth of its population.
It's also true that ever since the Trumpets of Revelation, those strange monsters have shown up everywhere.
That being said, humans aren't that weak.
We've begun to recover.
Recover?
Our organization is spearheading that effort.
We're gathering up the remaining humans in order to take back our world.
Just who are you?
I'm Ichinose Guren, a lieutenant colonel.
I'm part of the Japanese Imperial Demon Army.
Come with me and you'll be able to kill plenty of vampires.
Give him this.
You despise them, don't you?
I do.
Then come with me.
I'll grant you the power you need.
Or so he said, that stupid Guren.
It's been four years already, for crying out loud.
Totally not feeling club stuff...
Hey, let's grab some ice cream on the way home!
"Wait up! I love ice cream too!"
How about using that to approach them?
What's up with you?
You're being so familiar.
Lieutenant Colonel Guren told me about you.
Your entire family was killed by vampires when you were a kid,
and as a result you're now unable to connect with other people.
You're scared of losing someone close to you again.
Consequently, friends, allies and even lovers are all out of the question for you.
Why, you...
Stop going on as if you know me!
There, you just connected with me.
Don't joke around.
Go tell that idiot to let me into the vampire extermination unit already!
Besides, I'm more than strong enough to take them on.
He thought you'd say that and told me to give you this.
What, so Guren knew that all along?
"We don't need amateurs who can't make friends or lovers.
If you don't like it, find some buddies and introduce them to me.
Not that I expect you to be able to."
First you, now him...
You're all just making fun of me, damn it!
What is it with you?
Just how long are you going to follow me around?
Isn't this enough?
No, it's not.
You are to be kept under surveillance.
I have to report any problems to the Lieutenant Colonel.
P-Please stop it.
Stop?
We're friends, right? We're just asking you to go in our place.
Peaceful around here, huh?
Well, I'm going home.
Based on your reaction to that, it seems like you really will have a tough time making friends.
You want to be our buddy, right?
Then work for it!
Just like the livestock you are!
Hey, you listening?
Hey, lay off him.
Huh?
Who the hell are you?
Oh?
Contrary to what I was told,
you're actually a good person, aren't you?
Well, well, look what we have here.
You tryin' to be some kind of hero?
Or are you saying you'll take Yoichi's place?
Wow, you guys are like an open book.
Makes me kind of happy.
Huh?
Great, so we're gonna fight?
You wanna go?
Come on!
Oh, I forgot to tell you. If you hurt any civilians, your suspension will be extended.
Why do I have to do this?
Why me?
I-I'm sorry. It's all my fault...
Hey, Shinoa, you carry something too.
Ha, good one!
This girl...
I-I'm sorry...
And stop apologizing all the time!
Sheesh, what's up with you anyway?
Why were they bullying you?
They weren't...
Right, that's what all the bullied kids say.
I'm serious! They really weren't bullying me.
I wanted to be Yamanaka-kun's friend because I had a favor to ask of him.
Who's this Yamanaka anyway?
I see. You must be an idiot.
He's the one who hit you, Hyakuya-kun.
Oh, him.
So, what was this favor?
I failed the Imperial Demon Army's
enlistment exam, but I really want to join.
I heard that Yamanaka-kun was offered a spot in the vampire extermination unit, the Moon Demon Company.
The Moon Demon Company!? That guy?
Even though they won't let me in?
That punk Guren! I'll kill him!
S-So I thought I might get another chance
at the exam if Yamanaka-kun recommended me.
I know it's weird.
Someone as weak as me in the army...
But...
But?
No matter what it takes, I have to get revenge for my sister.
Revenge?
She died protecting me.
Back then, I didn't help her, so...
That's why...
Idiot. You'd be dead if you had.
It's not your fault.
But—
No buts!
Look, I don't want to burst your bubble, but give up on being enlisted.
Besides, I don't think your sister wants revenge anyway.
In a vampire extermination unit,
a weakling like you would just get in the way.
Emergency! This is an alert for all students and faculty.
A vampire has escaped from a nearby research facility.
Why is there a vampire here?
There's a vampire in the school?
Shut up for a bit!
Vampires regain their power by drinking blood.
As such, do not approach the vampire!
You two, get out of here! I'll call the Moon Demon Company!
I repeat...
No need!
I'll kill the vampire!
What?
I'll kill the real thing and force Guren to let me join!
H-Hey!
Hyakuya-kun!
That idiot.
That idiot!
Why is there a vampire here!?
Didn't the Imperial Demon Army guys say it was safe here?
Hey, hurry up!
Let me through!
Y-You're...
So, it's been four years.
I've finally found one of you...
Vampire...
prepare to die!
Human...
Yamanaka, take this girl and go! Hurry!
Aren't you supposed to be an army cadet?
Hurry up and...
That was just a lie.
What?
I thought everyone would respect me if I said I had been recruited...
You insolent livestock.
If you're going to stand in my way...
I'll just suck you dry, too.
Playtime is over. Ultimately, you couldn't save anyone.
Once I drink her blood and recover,
there will be nothing more you can do to stop me.
Stop!
Hyakuya-kun!
Yoichi!
You...
That wasn't half bad, Yoichi.
Well, we're friends.
Damn you!
Hyakuya-kun!
That's not nearly enough to kill me.
And you were so close, too.
I'll drink your blood before the Moon Demon Company gets here.
Yo, you called?
Damn, a demon weapon?
That's enough out of you, vampire.
You look like a mess.
Anyway, are you an idiot?
Did you seriously think you could hunt a vampire with a weapon that lacks anti-vampire enhancements?
D-Don't butt in!
A little bit more and I would've had her.
Oh?
I'm serious!
Oh, really?
But... I suppose you did pretty well for a brat.
Thanks to you, we got through this with fewer casualties.
You protected your friends.
So that's the Moon Demon Company.
I have no interest in friends.
Anyway, you've seen what I can do!
I can take on a vampire.
So just let me into the Moon Demon Company already!
Sorry, kid. I hate people with no sense of teamwork.
But you're the worst at teamwork, Lieutenant Colonel.
Huh?
What'd you say?
Oh, nothing.
Anyway,  it's just like Shinoa told you.
If you can't even make friends here—
Friends this, friends that. Enough!
I don't need friends to kill vampires!
Oh, thank goodness!
Huh?
Hyakuya-kun, you're okay!
I thought you had died.
Who's that?
Looks like a friend. More or less.
Hey, Hyakuya-kun?
S-Someone, call an ambulance!
Looks like you'll have to keep your promise now, Lieutenant Colonel.
Huh?
What? You've got to be kidding!
Just by closing my eyes, I can visualize that scene.
A scene of my precious family, friends and their smiles...
And...
I'm so glad you've finally made some friends, Yuu-chan.
Huh?
Why are you all...
Now we can finally rest in peace.
I mean, you're too kind to have your life revolve around revenge.
So...
be sure to treasure your new friends.
Anyway, we're gonna get going.
H-Hey, wait!
What are you talking about, Mika?
Not that way!
Wait! Wait, Mika!
Hyakuya-kun!
Thank goodness!
Shinoa-san, Hyakuya-kun woke up!
Oh, you're awake?
It's been decided that starting today,
you'll be joining the vampire extermination unit.
Huh?
That's great, Hyakuya-kun!
Ah, Saotome Yoichi-san, your application was also accepted.
They found your willingness to throw yourself into danger for your friends admirable.
In other words, like it or not, we're all teammates now.
Welcome to the Moon Demon Company.
Come on, Hyakuya-kun, you too.
Really?
Damn it.
I'm counting on you.
Nejireta shi no torikago sumi
The twisted cage of death I've been living in
kogoeta tsubomi mo
and the frozen flower bud too
okizari go away
leave them behind and go away
Kurameita kioku no kage
The shadows of my memory are dizzying
I need your blood
You need love tonight
I've got to rely
kagi wo akete miyou to
I'm trying to open a lock
kojiaketa reason  ga
by breaking through into reason
tada heikou ni narabu
but nothing will connect
Come and break it down for me
Remember where I'm from
kiganai hoshi demo
Even on this indifferent planet
negai nasazu
I can't make your wish come true
zange sae kowai n da
I'm even too afraid to apologize
yo doushiyou
So, what should I do?
kanadeta oto nado
The sounds that I played
komorebi no aka ga sawagu
rustled through the leaves in crimson light
Next time on Owari no Seraph:
The Demon Within
The Demon Within.